<Root><TimeEntry><ConName>Hourly</ConName><TimeEntryDate>2026-01-23</TimeEntryDate><Title>Arc from Cam called in regarding the 3cx set-up</Title><TimeDiff> - 
0.85 hrs</TimeDiff><Notes>&lt;span data-teams="true"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arc from Cam called in regarding the 3cx Setup from win-10 system to Win-11....&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So took the remote access of both the computer...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also login to the 3cx portal and verifiy the version details and Admin login details...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So informed Arc that we will set-up the 3cx in after-hours as if effect the serives...he understood...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Got the Call from ARC to start the 3cx set-up...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;so connected to the system and start the installation process...handover the task to next shift&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</Notes><Resource>S. Kumar
CHD-TS1
Support - Remote</Resource><Requestor>david@coastaero.com</Requestor><HourType>AH</HourType><BillRate>0.85 hrs / $150</BillRate><PODDet>CHD-TS1
Support
Remote</PODDet><InvDescription>Support Contract 
Hourly 
After-Hours</InvDescription><InvDetID>216408</InvDetID><StartDateTime>2026-01-23T01:24:00</StartDateTime><EndDateTime>2026-01-23T02:15:00</EndDateTime><Office-POD>CHD-TS1</Office-POD><RoleType>Support</RoleType><WorkType>Remote</WorkType><AssignedName>S. Kumar</AssignedName><AH_Rate>150.0000</AH_Rate><NH_Rate>0.0000</NH_Rate><AH_HoursWorked>0.85</AH_HoursWorked><NH_HoursWorked>0.00</NH_HoursWorked><Qty>0.85</Qty><Category>User Generated</Category></TimeEntry><TimeEntry><ConName>Hourly</ConName><TimeEntryDate>2026-01-23</TimeEntryDate><Title>Arc from Cam called in regarding the 3cx set-up</Title><TimeDiff> - 
2.17 hrs</TimeDiff><Notes>Surinder transferred the call from Arc, and Cam called in regarding the 3CX setup migration from the old system to the new system. I took remote access of both computers. They had already taken the 3CX backup, so we began the installation process; however, the application was not launching as expected.&lt;br /&gt;I removed the installation, rebooted the new machine, reinstalled 3CX, and restored the backup. The process took some time, but eventually the portal came up successfully.&lt;br /&gt;As requested, we powered off the old system and assigned its IP address to the new server, since they did not want to modify the existing Barracuda firewall rules. After assigning the old server&amp;rsquo;s IP, we verified that all extensions were showing correctly. The old server was powered off, and outbound calls were confirmed to be working.&lt;br /&gt;However, there was an issue with incoming calls. We performed a firewall test, disabled the firewall on the machine, and also disabled their ESET antivirus, but the incoming call issue persisted. There were pending updates on 3CX, so we attempted the update and rebooted the machine.&lt;br /&gt;Upon their request to revert the changes, we powered off the new server, powered on the old server again, reassigned the same internal IP to it, and verified that both incoming and outgoing calls were working fine. They will schedule the migration again at a later time.</Notes><Resource>G. Kumar
CHD-TS1
Support - Remote</Resource><Requestor>david@coastaero.com</Requestor><HourType>AH</HourType><BillRate>N : 1.67 hrs / $150
AH : 0.50 hrs / $150</BillRate><PODDet>CHD-TS1
Support
Remote</PODDet><InvDescription>Support Contract 
Hourly 
After-Hours</InvDescription><InvDetID>216407</InvDetID><StartDateTime>2026-01-23T07:30:00</StartDateTime><EndDateTime>2026-01-23T09:40:00</EndDateTime><Office-POD>CHD-TS1</Office-POD><RoleType>Support</RoleType><WorkType>Remote</WorkType><AssignedName>G. Kumar</AssignedName><AH_Rate>150.0000</AH_Rate><NH_Rate>150.0000</NH_Rate><AH_HoursWorked>0.50</AH_HoursWorked><NH_HoursWorked>1.67</NH_HoursWorked><Qty>2.17</Qty><Category>My VOIP-SIP</Category></TimeEntry></Root>